Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 1 and District 1 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 1 Locals, 2.
  - Local 119
    - Local 119 Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1949 (Box 7, Folder 122)
      - Secretary of Jandreau to Blazik Regarding Wages, March 2, 1944; 66.
      - Jandreau to Blazik Regarding War Labor Board, Pattern Makers, and Wages, March 2, 1944; 67.
      - James Matles to Bersing Regarding Supplies and Finances, May 5, 1938; 68.
      - Norma Gould, Secretary of Matles, to Rhine Regarding Local 119 Constitution, February 3, 1943; 69.
      - Matles to Seiner Regarding Wages and Grievances, October 5, 1942; 70.
      - Matles to Seiner, November 6, 1942; 71.
      - Matles to Lavelle Regading Organization, November 28, 1947; 72.
      - Matles to Seiner Regarding Local 119 Anniversary Ball, January 20, 1943; 73.
      - Matles to Shoemaker Regarding Membership Meeting, February 25, 1943; 74.
      - Joseph Turkowski to Blazik Regarding Grievances, September 6, 1944; 75.
    - Local 119 Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1949 (Box 7, Folder 123)
      - Carl Bersing to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Maintenance of Membership, June 2, 1944; 1.
      - Louis Blazik Telegram to Emspak Regarding 1943 UE Convention, September 3, 1943; 2.
      - Blazik to Leo Jandreau Regarding Wages, February 9, 1944; 3.
      - Blazik to Jandreau Regarding War Labor Board, Grievances, Wages, and Patternmakers with Docket #741, February 10, 1944; 4.
      - Blazik to Jandreau Regarding Grievances and Wages with Jandreau Letter to Joseph Dermody and March 3, 1944, Henry Rhine Letter to Jandreau, March 4, 1944; 5.
      - Blazik to Emspak Regading GE Contract and No-Strike Pledge with GE Welches, May 3, 1944; 6.
      - Blazik to Dermody Regarding Grievances, August 9, 1944; 7.
      - Blazik to Emspak Regarding Dues, September 25, 1944; 8.
      - Blazik to Dermody Regarding Staff Members, August 25, 1945; 9.
      - Blazik to Emspak Regarding Finances and Organization, September 12, 1945; 10.
      - Blazik to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Wages, September 20, 1945; 11.
      - Blazik to Dermody Regarding Wages, November 29, 1945; 12.
      - Blazik to Joseph Turkowski Regarding Telephone, March 22, 1946; 13.
      - Blazik to Fitzgerald Regarding Anti-Communism and Factionalism, August 14, 1946; 14.
      - John Brennan to Tom Neil Regarding Veterans, February 1946; 15.
      - William Buchanan to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 1, 1944; 16.
      - Buchanan Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, November 18, 1949; 17.
      - Buchanan Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, November 21, 1949; 18.
      - David Davis to Emspak Regarding Political Action, August 6, 1943; 19.
      - Al Facone to Emspak Regarding UE Finances and Inter-union Rivalry, December 16, 1949; 20.
      - Linwood Ford to Jandreau Regarding Runaway Shops, Wages, and Grievances, November 4, 1943; 21.
      - Ford to UE Regarding Guards and Wages, February 9, 1944; 22.
      - Ford to Philip Murray Regarding Taft-Hartley and General Strike, May 12, 1949; 23.
      - William Hetrick to UE Regarding Finances, September 30, 1938; 24.
      - Hetrick to UE Regarding Finances, October 10, 1938; 25.
      - Hetrick to UE Regarding Supplies, January 20, 1939; 26.
      - Hetrick to UE Regarding Finances, March 1, 1939; 27.
      - Hetrick to Emspak Regarding Supplies, May 29, 1939; 28.
      - Hetrick to UE Regarding Supplies, August 22, 1939; 29.
      - William Hood to Emspak Regarding Second Front with Resolution, August 27, 1942; 30.
      - Hood to UE News Regarding Second Front, November 20, 1942; 31.
      - Edward Houchins to Fitzgerald Regarding Shop Stewards Banquet, January 13, 1948; 32.
      - Houchins to All Officers, Executive Board Members and Shop Stewards Regarding Annual Banquet, January 13, 1948; 33.
      - Jandreau to W.R. Borrows Regarding Unemployment and War Production Board with September 14, 1943, Borrows Letter to Emspak, October 8, 1943; 34.
      - P.A. Lavelle Telegram to Emspak Regarding 1946 Trials, November 16, 1946; 35.
      - Lavelle to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, February 20, 1947; 36.
      - Lavelle to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, March 6, 1947; 37.
      - Lavelle to James Matles Regarding White Collar Workers, November 19, 1947; 38.
      - Lavelle to Emspak Regarding Finances and White Collar Workers, May 14, 1948; 39.
      - John Lyons to UE Regarding Inter-union Rivalry with the Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians and White Collar Workers, October 27, 1943; 40.
      - Lyons to Emspak Regarding White Collar Workers, November 9, 1943; 41.
      - Lyons to Emspak Regarding White Collar Workers, December 30, 1943; 42.
      - Jack McDonough to Matles Regarding Organization at GE in Trenton, October 22, 1942; 43.
      - Vincent McLaughlin to Emspak Regarding Unemployment with April 11, 1949, Resolutions on Unemployment and Wage Increases & the Shorter Work Week, April 13, 1949; 44.
      - McLaughlin to Emspak Regarding Anti-Communism and 1949 UE Convention, October 20, 1949; 45.
      - Walter Mugford to Emspak Regarding Supplies, December 26, 1939; 46.
      - Mugford to Nathan Geller Regarding Finances, February 8, 1940; 47.
      - Mugford to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 5, 1939; 48.
      - Thomas O'Connor to UE Regarding Political Action Committee, July 3, 1946; 49.
      - O'Connor to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, November 6, 1946; 50.
      - Nelson Renwick to Emspak Regading Finances, March 14, 1940; 51.
      - Renwick to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Supplies, April 1940; 52.
      - Renwick to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 21, 1940; 53.
      - Renwick to Emspak Regarding Supplies, June 9, 1940; 54.
      - Renwick Telegram to UE Regarding Supplies, June 10, 1940; 55.
      - Renwick to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 28, 1940; 56.
      - Renwick to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Supplies, July 19, 1940; 57.
      - Renwick to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 9, 1940; 58.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Corruption and White Collar Workers, January 25, 1943; 59.
      - Rhine to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 119 Constitution, January 25, 1943; 60.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Local 119 Constitution, February 2, 1943; 61.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding Local 119 Constitution, Socialist Labor Party, and Cafeteria Workers with February 1, 1943, Program for Employees in the Cafeteria and Kitchen of the General Motors Plant, February 11, 1943; 62.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Membership Meeting, February 24, 1943; 63.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding Organization of Goods and Cafeteria Workers, February 26, 1943; 64.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, William Hood Case, and Anti-Communism, March 5, 1943; 65.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding Local 119 Officer Elections and Factionalism with Election Results, March 11, 1943; 66.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Organization, Time Study, and Wages with the Results after Four Weeks of the Drive and March 23, 1943, Report of the Third Week of the Drive, March 29, 1943; 67.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding Membership Meeting, March 31, 1943; 68.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding Organization, Factionalism, War Labor Board, and Patternmakers, April 2, 1943; 69.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Organization and Grievances with 1943 Progress Report on First Three Months and Plans for the Next Three Months, April 2, 1943; 70.
    - Local 119 Outgoing Correspondence, 1942-1949 (Box 7, Folder 124)
      - Harry Rhine to Julius Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Grievances with April 2, 1943, C.A. Shoemaker Letter to Executive Board Members, April 5, 1943; 1.
      - Rhine to James Matles Regarding Check-off, April 3-5, 1943; 2.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding Local 119 Grievances, April 27, 1943; 3.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Factionalism, Organization, and Major Grievances, April 28, 1943; 4.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Organization with May 4, 1943, Report and Recommendations, May 5, 1943; 5.
      - Rhine to Leo Jandreau and Emspak Regarding Factionalism, June 14, 1943; 6.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Organization and Factionalism with a Comparison of Local 119 Per Capita Reports for the First Six Months of 1943 and 1942 and a Draft of a Declaration of Policy for UE Local 119, June 17, 1943; 7.
      - Rhine to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism and Anti-Communism, June 17, 1943; 8.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Local 119 Factionalism, Grievances, and Constitution, June 17, 1943; 9.
      - Rhine to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 119 Contstitution, Factionalism, and Anti-Communism, July 2, 1943; 10.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Local 119 Factionalism, Women, and Constitution, July 5, 1943; 11.
      - Rhine to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 119 Constitution with Draft of Some of the Changes Made in Local 119's Constitution; a Reply to Charges by Seiner and Local 119 Officers in Their Letter of June 30, 1943; and "GE Workers" Leaflet, July 16, 1943; 12.
      - Rhine to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 119 Officer Elections and Factionalism, July 23, 1943; 13.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Local 119 Elections, Factionalism, Afro-Americans, and Anti-Communism, July 23, 1943; 14.
      - Rhine to Jandreau Regarding Grievances, July 24, 1943; 15.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding 1943 UE Convention, August 3, 1943; 16.
      - Rhine to Matles Regarding Grievances, August 3, 1943; 17.
      - Rhine to Jandreau Regarding Grievances, August 3, 1943; 18.
      - Rhine to Jandreau Regarding Unemployment, War Labor Board, and Grievances, August 23, 1943; 19.
      - Rhine to Jandreau Regarding Local 119 Contract at GE, August 23, 1943; 20.
      - Rhine to Jandreau Regarding Local 119 Unemployment, War Production Board, Contracts at GE and Turnover, August 31, 1943; 21.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, Elections, and Local 119 Officers with "Check the Record of all Candidates" and "Here is Your Chance!" Leaflets, October 3, 1943; 22.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Anti-Communism, October 13, 1943; 23.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Grievances, November 6, 1943; 24.
      - Rhine to Jandreau Regarding Millwrights, Wages, and War Labor Board, November 13, 1943; 25.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding White Collar Workers, November 30, 1943; 26.
      - Rhine to Jandreau Regarding Shop Stewards Meeting, November 30, 1943; 27.
      - Rhine to Jandreau Regarding Stewards, January 6, 1944; 28.
      - Rhine to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 3, 1944; 29.
      - Francis Scannell to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 18, 1947; 30.
      - Scannell to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 5, 1947; 31.
      - Walter Schandein, Jr. Regarding Supplies, January 12, 1945; 32.
      - Milton Seiner to UE News Regarding Mailing List, August 1940; 33.
      - Seiner to Thomas Wright Regarding Second Front, September 30, 1942; 34.
      - Seiner Telegram to Emspak Regarding Local 119 Officers, October 17, 1942; 35.
      - Seiner to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Organization, October 26, 1942; 36.
      - Seiner to Emspak Regarding Local 119 Anniversary Ball with Two Tickets, December 24, 1942; 37.
      - Seiner to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 119 Anniversary Ball, December 24, 1942; 38.
      - Seiner to Matles Regarding Supplies, December 31, 1942; 39.
      - Seiner to Emspak Regarding William Hood Case and Factionalism, January 12, 1943; 40.
      - Seiner to Emspak Regarding Women, Factionalism, and Anti-Communism, March 9, 1943; 41.
      - Seiner to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, July 1, 1943; 42.
      - C.A. Shoemaker to Emspak Regarding Address Correction, January 23, 1943; 43.
      - Shoemaker to Emspak Regarding Local 119 Contract and GE Arbitration, February 9, 1943; 44.
      - Shoemaker to Philip Murray Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations, February 11, 1943; 45.
      - Shoemaker to Emspak Regarding Organization, February 23, 1943; 46.
      - Shoemaker to Matles Regarding Membership Meeting, March 3, 1943; 47.
      - Shoemaker to Emspak Regarding Farmer's Educational and Co-operative Union of America, April 26, 1943; 48.
      - Shoemaker to All Stewards Regarding Stewards Council and Organization, April 29, 1943; 49.
      - Shoemaker to Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meeting and Organization, May 17, 1943; 50.
      - Shoemaker to Fitzgerald Regarding Membership Meeting, June 26, 1943; 51.
      - Shoemaker to All Stewards Regarding Local 119 Constitution, June 1943; 52.
      - Shoemaker to Jandreau Regarding Grievances, July 21, 1943; 53.
      - Shoemaker to Jandreau Regarding Stewards Council, July 22, 1943; 54.
      - Shoemaker to UE Regarding No-Strike Pledge with Resolution, August 4, 1943; 55.
      - Shoemaker to Jandreau Regarding Stewards Council and White Collar Workers, August 13, 1943; 56.
      - Shoemaker to Jandreau Regarding Stewards Council and White Collar Workers, August 19, 1943; 57.
      - Shoemaker to All Stewards Regarding Stewards Meeting, August 1943; 58.
      - Philip Van Gelder to Matles Regarding Factionalism and 1949 UE Convention with Two Slate Cards, July 12, 1949; 59.
      - Local 119 Executive Board to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, June 30, 1943; 60.
      - Executive Board to Emspak Regarding Wages, September 30, 1943; 61.
      - Local 119 Member to UE Regarding Factionalism and Anti-Communism, February 1947; 62.
    - Local 119 Salary/Expense Letters, William Renwick, Decembre 13, 1940-December 1, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Local 119 Receipts, 1938-1940 (Box 7, Folder 126)
      - William Hetrick, October 8, 1938-January 4, 1940; 1-15.
      - Wilson Renwick, January 15-August 12, 1940; 16-26.
      - Renwick with Receipt #10918, August 20, 1940; 27.
      - UE Local 119, August 31, 1940; 28.
    - Local 119 Per Capita Records, September 30, 1938-August 8, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Local 119 Supply Requisitions, 1937-1940 (Box 7, Folder 128)
      - William Howard, October 6, 1937; 1.
      - J. Patterson, January 27, 1938; 2.
      - William Renwick, August 12, 1938; 3.
      - William Hetrick, February 2-March 2, 1939; 4-5.
      - Walter Mugford, December 29, 1939; 6-7.
      - Edward Nevins with Memo Regarding Order, March 5, 1940; 8.
      - Mugford, May 20, 1940; 9.
      - Renwick, June 9-August 27, 1940; 10-14.
    - Local 119 Stamps, 1938-1940 (Box 7, Folder 129)
      - William Hetrick, October 8-28, 1938; 1-2.
      - Wilson Renwick, March 1-August 15, 1940; 3-7.
    - Local 119 Shipment Notices, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 130)
      - William Hetrick, February 4, 1939; 1.
      - Edward Nevins, March 7, 1940; 2.
      - Wilson Renwick, April 2, 1940; 3.
      - UE Local 119, May 21, 1940; 4.
      - Renwick, June 18, 1940; 5.
      - UE Local 119, August 31, 1940; 6.
    - Local 119 Notices of Delinquency/Suspension, 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 131)
      - Delinquency, May 1938; 1.
      - Delinquency, October 1938; 2.
      - Delinquency, December 1938; 3.
      - Delinquency, February 1939; 4.
      - Delinquency, April 1, 1939; 5.
      - Delinquency, June 1939; 6.
      - Delinquency, July 1939; 7.
      - Delinquency, August 1939; 8.
      - Delinquency, September 1939; 9.
      - Delinquency, November 1939; 10.
      - Suspension, July 30, 1938; 11.
      - Suspension, May 1, 1939; 12.
      - Suspension, December 1, 1939; 13.
    - Local 119 Credit Bills, December 28, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Local 119 Miscellaneous, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 133)
      - American Arbitration Association Bill, June 10, 1949; 1.
      - Emma Memo to Paula, October 2, 1950; 2.
      - Novelty Printing Company to Local 119 Regarding Balance of Payment with 1949-1950 Duplicate Bills, 3.
    - Local 119 William Hood Case (Box 7, Folder 134)
      - Local 119 Resolution, December 14, 1942; 1.
      - William Hood to James Matles, December 21, 1942; 2.
      - Norma Gould, Secretary of Matles, to Hood, December 23, 1942; 3.
      - Hood to Matles, December 30, 1942; 4.
      - Hood to Julius Emspak, January 2, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to Milton Seiner, January 4, 1943; 6.
      - Russ Nixon Telegram to Matles, January 4, 1943; 7.
      - UE District Council Meeting Notes, January 7, 1943; 8.
      - Local 119 Membership Meeting Notes, January 11, 1943; 9.
      - Hood to Emspak, January 12, 1943; 10.
      - Seiner to Emspak, January 12, 1943; 11.
      - Henry Rhine to Matles, January 13, 1943; 12.
      - Francis White to Emspak, January 18, 1943; 13.
      - Emspak to White, January 21, 1943; 14.
      - Hood to Emspak, January 22, 1943; 15.
      - Hood to Emspak, January 28, 1943; 16.
      - Emspak to White, January 29, 1943; 17.
      - Emspak to Rhine, January 29, 1943; 18.
      - Emspak to Seiner, January 29, 1943; 19.
      - Report on Membership Meeting of UE Local 119, February 10, 1943; 20.
      - Rhine to Matles, February 10, 1943; 21.
      - Irma Spritz to Emspak, February 13, 1943; 22.
      - Emspak to Frank Eubank, February 25, 1943; 23.
      - John Lyons to Emspak, February 25, 1943; 24.
      - Emspak to Rhine, March 1, 1943; 25.
      - Emspak to Lyons, March 1, 1943; 26.
      - Rhine to Emspak, March 2, 1943; 27.
      - Rhine to Matles with Local 119 Election of Executive Board Members, March 5, 1943; 28.
      - Rhine to Emspak, March 5, 1943; 29.
      - Emspak to Lyons, March 6, 1943; 30.
      - Emspak to Rhine, March 6, 1943; 31.
    - Local 119 Organization Drive, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 135)
      - Outline of Organizational Activity Between November 1 and March 1, 1943, 1.
      - Report of Organizing Committee, February 8, 1943; 2.
      - Report on Organization Drive, March 16, 1943; 3.
      - Report on Local 119 Membership Meeting, March 17, 1943; 4.
      - Report on 1st Week of Drive, March 1943; 5.
      - Two Weeks - Two Hundred New Members, March 1943; 6.
      - Progress Report on First Three Months and Plans for the Next Three Months, April 1943; 7.
      - Recommendations of the Organizing Committee to Membership Meeting, May 10, 1943; 8.
      - Dues and Initiation Payments, July 12, 1943; 9.
    - Local 119 White Collar Workers, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 136)
      - GE Office Workers with June 25, 1945, Henry Rhine Letter to Julius Emspak, June 22, 1945; 1.
      - GE Office Workers with June 27, 1945, Rhine Letter to Emspak, 2.
      - Basic Proposals for Supplemental Agreement for Salary Workers, 3.
    - Local 119 Trenton Strike, 1942-1943 (Box 7, Folder 137)
      - Local 119 Executive Board Letter to Local 119, November 23, 1942; 1.
      - Henry Rhine to James Matles, February 6, 1943; 2.
      - R. Paxton to W.R. Burrows, February 6, 1943; 3.
    - Local 119 Cafeteria Organizing Campaign, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 138)
      - Duffy and Henry Rhine to Milton Seiner, January 22, 1943; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Rhine, February 25, 1943; 2.
    - Local 119 Miscellaneous Special Topics, 1943-1947, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 139)
      - Adjustment Committee Report, June 28, 1943; 1.
      - Final Special Meeting on Local 119 Constitution, June 28, 1943; 2.
      - Delegates to District Council, October 10, 1947; 3.
      - A Declaration of Policy, 4.
    - Local 119 Newspapers, Union News, January 1943-May 1948 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - Local 119 Newspapers, General Electric News, March 1, 1940-February 5, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - Local 119 Pamphlets, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 142)
      - Inflation and Wages, 1.
      - Socialist Industrial Unionism, 2.
    - Local 119 Leaflets, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 143)
      - "We Are On Our Way", March 5, 1943; 1.
      - "Open Meeting of All 2nd Shift Employees", March 15, 1943; 2.
      - "For All GE Workers", July 12, 1943; 3.
      - "Monday Night", November 8, 1943; 4.
    - Local 119 Miscellaneous Publications, 1943, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 144)
      - Clipping from Philadelphia Works News, August 20, 1943; 1.
      - Election Card, 2.
  - Local 120 (Philadelphia)
    - Local 120 (Philadelphia) Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Julius Emspak to Patrick McNamee Regarding Finances, November 11, 1938; 1.
      - Emspak to William McBride Regarding Finances, December 6, 1938; 2.
      - Emspak to McBride Regarding Finances, December 13, 1938; 3.
      - Emspak to Edward Saleski Regarding Finances, December 22, 1938; 4.
      - Emspak to Harry Block Regarding Runaway Shops, September 20, 1939; 5.
    - Local 120 (Philadelphia) Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - James Beard to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, September 27, 1938; 1.
      - Beard to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 1, 1938; 2.
      - Harry Block to UE Regarding Finances, November 1, 1938; 3.
      - William McBride to UE Regarding Finances, November 24, 1938; 4.
      - McBride to UE Regarding Finances, December 26, 1938; 5.
      - McBride to UE Regarding Finances, February 21, 1939; 6.
      - McBride to UE Regarding Finances, April 19, 1939; 7.
      - Edward Saleski to Emspak Regarding Local 120 Officers, December 17, 1938; 8.
      - Saleski to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 28, 1938; 9.
    - Local 120 (Philadelphia) Receipts, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - James W. Beard, September 29, 1938; 1.
      - H.R. Walsh (Baltimore), October 10, 1938; 2.
      - Beard, November 3, 1938; 3.
      - William McBride, November 28, 1938-May 18, 1939; 4-11.
    - Local 120 (Philadelphia) Per Capita Reports, September 27, 1938-May 17, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Local 120 (Philadelphia) Supply Requisitions, 1938-1939 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - James W. Beard, September 20, 1938; 1.
      - H.R. Walsh (Baltimore), October 4, 1938; 2.
      - William McBride, December 8, 1938-April 19, 1939; 3-4.
    - Local 120 (Philadelphia) Stamps, James W. Beard, August 19, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Local 120 (Philadelphia) Notices of Delinquency/Suspension, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Delinquency, June 1939; 1.
      - Suspension, July 20, 1939; 2.
    - Local 120 (Philadelphia) Credit Bills, August 23, 1938-July 23, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Local 120 (Philadelphia) Miscellaneous, Postal Receipt, July 18, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Local 120 (Wilmington)
    - Local 120 (Wilmington) Officers Lists, February 29-October 31, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Local 120 (Wilmington) Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1946 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Julius Emspak to Harry Block Regarding Organization, December 27, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Block Regarding Organization, January 12, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Sam Goldberg Regarding Supplies, January 12, 1944; 3.
      - Emspak to Philip Saba Regarding Finances, May 1, 1945; 4.
      - Emspak to Dorothy Sullivan Regarding Finances, March 1, 1946; 5.
      - Emspak to Joe Stensky Regarding Finances, August 21, 1946; 6.
      - David Ratner to Local 120 Regarding Finances, September 25, 1945; 7.
      - Ratner to William Beck Regarding Finances, November 6, 1946; 8.
    - Local 120 (Wilmington) Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - William Beck to Julius Emspak Regardng Finances, January 20, 1945; 1.
      - Beck to UE Regarding Finances, February 10, 1945; 2.
      - Harry Block to Emspak Regarding Organization, January 6, 1944; 3.
      - William Branton to Philip Murray Regarding Wages and Hours with January 20, 1945, Letters from Molly Lynch, Secretary of Murray, to Walter Branton and Albert Fitzgerald and January 29, 1945, Ray Klausner Letter to Peter Besch, January 17, 1945; 4.
      - Samuel Goldberg to Emspak Regarding Organization, December 16, 1943; 5.
      - Philip Saba to Emspak Regarding Organization and Finances, May 3, 1945; 6.
    - Local 120 (Wilmington) Notices of Delinquency/Suspension, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 13)